import 'Catalog/en/foreign-languages/greek/greek.css';

// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/gb.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],


}



export var cards = {
  "alpha": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>α</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "alpha"
  },
  "beta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>β</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "beta"
  },
  "gamma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>γ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "gamma"
  },
  "delta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>δ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "delta"
  },
  "epsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ε</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "epsilon"
  },
  "zeta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ζ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "zeta"
  },
  "eta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>η</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "eta"
  },
  "theta": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>θ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "theta"
  },
  "iota": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ι</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "iota"
  },
  "kappa": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>κ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "kappa"
  },
  "lambda": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>λ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "lambda"
  },
  "mu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>μ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "mu"
  },
  "nu": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ν</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "nu"
  },
  "xi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ξ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "xi"
  },
  "omicron": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ο</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "omicron"
  },
  "pi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>π</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "pi"
  },
  "rho": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ρ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "rho"
  },
  "sigma": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>σ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "sigma"
  },
  "tau": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>τ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "tau"
  },
  "upsilon": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>υ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "upsilon"
  },
  "phi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>φ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "phi"
  },
  "chi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>χ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "chi"
  },
  "psi": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ψ</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "psi"
  },
  "omega": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '<greek>ω</greek>',
    prompt: "Name this letter",
    answer: "omega"
  }
};